Hello.
My name is Gabriela Garzon at G.G.
Image and Etiquette Consulting in Miami, Florida.
In this clip, I'm going to talk about how to build a spring wardrobe for women.
Basically, you're doing a transition here, so here you can start using like whites, and light pastels.
Basically try to have like light dresses.
This is like a very nice flowy white dress that you can transition into the summer, or you can start using like khaki's with like pastel colors, like the pink type of sweaters that you can just go ahead and layer on top of like pant tops or crew neck type of tops, and other type of sweaters with different neck lines.
You can start using really fun jackets, because it's still, you know it's still a little cool, and you can just always want to try and cover yourself with cool things and bright colors, and happy colors.
And if it get, if it starts getting chilly, you can use like, you know like very light type of pastel color trench coats and of course, you should have boots so you can wear the dresses with the boots, closed toe heels, and just fun accessories.
Once again, this is Gabbie at G.G.
Image and Etiquette Consulting.